Ending the matter! Whitebeard versus the Blackbeard Pirates!
Shitty you. What's going on? What happened at Impelled Down? I have a hunch that Magellan didn't release you. How did you make it to Marineford?
Well, old friend. Maybe you ought to worry less about how we got here, and worry more about what you're going to do now that we are.
Z-hahaha!
If you want to find out more, check out Impelled Down later. That'll give you an idea. By the way, I'm switching sides in case you couldn't tell. Figured you might want to know that.
Lead Admiral Sengoku! I'm sorry I wasn't able to inform you sooner, sir.
We received a report that the Gates of Justice opened a second time, and an unidentified ship was able to pass through!
So that's how they made it. But the control room is under Navy operation. Nothing else unusual was reported either.
So how could you slip past us undetected?
Oh! That's where I'll take credit.
Huh?
Allow me to explain.
Rapscallions that we are, we crashed the party at Impelled Down and picked up your old friend.
Then I thought I'd have a spot of fun and hypnotize the Navy soldiers in the control room.
I made them open the Gates of Justice for any Navy ship that approached.
Incidentally, that seems to have helped a few other rogues get through as well.
Straw Hat is allies.
And since I was considered a Navy ally, I got through just fine.
If it weren't for my title, I couldn't have made it inside the prison either.
Long story short, being a warlord made this little operation a cinch.
But now I'm through with you!
You used us just to bolster the ranks of your crew?
The old soldier finally figured it out!
My plan is almost complete now!
You'll see soon enough!
Let's finish this, you damn traitor!
олнititch!
Captain! Incoming!
Incoming!
Aaaaaaah!
Yeah, that was close!
Good to see our reflexes are still in order!
So much for old times!
Guess I can't blame you!
Of all the pirates who have called the Moby Dick their home,
you're the only one I refuse to call my son, Cheech.
There is only one rule I have on my ship and you dared to break it.
You betrayed our trust by killing your fellow mate.
It's time to put an end to this.
You'll pay for 4th Division Commander Thatcher's death with your life.
Mark my words, he will be avenged.
Pops, what are you doing?
Marco!
Let me help you!
Listen, you stay out of this one, boy.
But you're hurt!
Did you hear me?
Let's get this over with.
Right now!
See?
What do you think I'm here for?
What's that black stuff coming out of his body?
Is that... smoke?
Smoke?
Enjoy this black hole!
This devil fruit power's exactly why I killed Vatch.
I knew I had to have it.
Dark, dark fruit's real tasty.
Why don't you give it a try?
Don't worry, there's plenty to go around.
You know there's a pattern.
First Thatch kicks the bucket and now Ace has followed suit.
All your top underlings seem to be dropping like flies and you're too old to do a damn thing about it.
Good thing I'm no longer under your thumb.
If I hadn't have gotten out when I did, who knows where I would have ended up.
But I'll have you know, I spared him at Bonnaroo Island when I could have killed him.
I will not stand for this!
Easy now, don't even bother me.
Your power won't work against me, no devil fruit power will!
Vortex!
This darkness of mine is pretty handy, ain't it?
I can nullify your fancy little tricks just like I did with good old Ace.
In other words, no more earthquakes!
Not against me!
What just happened? Nobody can hit Pops that easily.
No you don't!
Didn't you hear what I just said?
You're not gonna hit me with that!
Severe old man!
Come on, don't be such a sore loser!
You're a loser!
Ow!
Damn!
My arm!
You're arrogant, a fool!
You were never fit to be in my crew!
Hey! Hold on!
Pops, please don't!
I'm your son, Pops!
Stop it!
You would gun your own son!
I'm your son!
He did it!
Here you go, Pops!
Huh?
Halo!
He's still alive!
Alright!
Looks like he's still got some fight in him!
One more hit on it to it!
Come on, Pops!
Just one more!
Finish him off!
Come on, Pops!
Hey, Pops!
What's going on?
He isn't budging.
He's taking on a lot of damage today.
Huh?
He isn't budging.
He's taking on a lot of damage today.
Huh?
On top of his worsening health.
All this fighting is starting to take its toll.
Pops is still strong, but his body is…
when he hasn't에요…
Pops is still strong, but the body is…
All this fighting is starting to take its toll.
Pops is still strong, but his body is…
Get away from me, you monster!
I said get away from me!
Dammit! Will you just die already?
No, don't do it!
Finish him off!
Hooray!
Cruelly…
Oh God God!
He będziemy shuck off.
Ah ha ha ha ha!
Ah ha ha ha!
That's right! Keep shirting him till he's dead!
Fight back, Pops!
Come on, Pops!
Please don't die!
What do you mean, Roger? You're going to die?
Yeah, I could just feel it.
Do you want to know how to get to Raptal?
I could tell you, if you'd like.
Don't bother. I've got no interest in that place.
Ah, those World Cup McClowns don't know what they're doing.
Do you know what they've been calling me these days?
They call me Gold Roger.
Hmm? So what? I thought that was your name.
Do you want to go buy something else now?
No, no, you don't get it!
My real name is Gold D, Roger.
Every now and then I come across someone with a D in their name.
Like my crew member, Marshal D. Teach.
So, what does the D stand for?
That? You want to know, huh?
Ha! Fine, fine. I can tell you.
It's a story from way back when.
Hey! I'm out of bullets! Someone give me another gun!
That won't be necessary.
Whitebeard's unconscious. The man's done for.
You could nudge him with your pinky and he'd topple over like a domino.
It's not you, Teach.
No way! He's still alive!
The man that Gold D. Roger was waiting for.
It's not you, Teach. Not a damn chance.
Huh?
Just as there are people out there who inherited Roger's will.
Soon enough, someone will carry on in Ace's name as well.
You may try to destroy their spirit, but you will never extinguish their flame.
So it has been.
And so it shall continue to be from now till the very end of time.
And one day in the future, when we're all dead and gone,
someone will arise carrying generations upon generations of our history on his shoulders.
And he'll throw down the gauntlet in front of the entire world.
Sengoku, you and the government know what's coming.
A war that will embroil the seas far and wide.
That's why you're so afraid.
Though nothing you do will stop it.
I've no interest in it myself.
But someday that treasure will turn this world upside down.
You know what I'm talking about.
And I'm sure that someone will find it.
Whether you like it or not, that day will come soon.
The One Piece!
The One Piece is real!
The Two Piece!
The One Piece!
He likes the One Piece!
The Two Piece!
See the One Piece!
And he gets to Ben!
You bastard!
Now that was a touching conclusion!
Don't leave us!
It's over.
Forgive me, my sons.
I raised a fool, and I couldn't take responsibility.
But you boys gave me everything I could have ever wanted out of life.
I've reached the end of my voyage.
It's been a long and fulfilling journey.
Let's sail out!
I couldn't have asked for more.
You don't even care about treasure? Why else would you be in the game?
Well, fine. What are you looking for then?
Hey! You listening, Newgate?
There's only one thing I need.
And I've wanted it since I was a kid.
Huh? I thought so!
Spill the beans!
I want a family.
A family?
That's a joke, right?
I am deeply grateful.
Goodbye, my sons.
Huh?
Farewell.
He's dead!
I can't believe that bastard!
He just died on his feet!
And so, Whitebeard passes.
Even after death, his body remains upright.
The haunting image of his battered body, which mowed down his enemies, was a sight to behold.
The final tally of sword wounds he received in this battle was no less than 267.
The number of gunshot wounds, 152.
He was struck by cannonballs 46 times.
And yet, if you were to look upon the proud back of this great man, you would see that in this battle, and indeed his entire life as a pirate, it remained unmarred by any sign of retreat.
Not content with the deaths of Ace and Whitebeard, the Navy seeks to wipe out every last pirate, even as they retreat.
In the midst of the fray, Lakainu sets his eyes on the unconscious Luffy.
Meanwhile, Blackbeard reveals his true scheme and a terrifying new power.
On the next One Piece, the show begins! Blackbeard's blood is revealed! I'm gonna be king of the pirates!